[PC

Trek](https://www.pctrek.com/)

Privacy Policy
==============

###### PRIVACY POLICY

This site values it's user's privacy. We are committed to ethical delivery advertising recommendation and delivery of recommended products. We do not collect any personally identifiable information. In simple language this means, we don't know the name, gender, age, email, and interests of any users.

This privacy policy covers the privacy rules associated with user's interaction with this website's services or products and recommended advertiser which are presented to end users via other partner software products. User's must review the partner software product's own privacy policy and in addition review the privacy policy of any advertiser product recommended by this site.

###### WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY

While visiting our websites, we may send your browser a cookie which is stored in your browser and allows us to identify it. Cookies are used to help better understand our user's product interest. In addition, our website includes traffic tracking software which simply tracks the number of visits to our site and usage of our site.

We collect the following types of information from site visitors:

* Site usage information
    
* Customer & Site Feedback
    
* Newsletter Registration
    
* Purchase Track of a customers

###### USAGE OF COLLECTED DATA

Any information collected is anonymous. We do not sell or otherwise market this information to third parties. We may from time to time share with advertisers non-personally identifiable information for them to improve the performance of their products. We may share information if required to:

* (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order;
    
* (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues;
    
* (3) enforce this Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between you and this site, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or
    
* (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of this site, its visitors, users and/or the public.

###### NEWSLETTER REGISTRATION

If you like to subscribe for the free email newsletter, you will receive emails with information about products, company, industry news, events, promotions and campaigns. You can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom in every newsletter.

###### PURCHASES

If you purchase one of our products, the payment will be handled by a 3rd party payment gateway. The payment gateways will collect information about you, such as your name, address, phone number, email and credit card details. A very limited amount of information acquired from this is shared with us, which enables us to setup your account as a customer with us. Financial details such as credit card information, etc. are not shared with us.

###### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

###### LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

In no event will PC Trek products be liable for any damages, including without limitation, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, whether under a contract, tort or any other theory of liability, arising in connection with any party's use of the website or in connection with any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, line system failure, loss of data, or loss of use related to this website or any website operated by any third party or any contents of this website or any other website, even if PC Trek products are aware of the possibility of such damages.

###### ADVERTISING

By accessing the site and downloading the software products, you hereby grant us permission to display promotional information, advertisements, and offers for third party products or services (collectively "Advertising"). Advertising contains third party advertiser products. Each advertiser product recommended has its own privacy policy which each user can freely review before accepting any recommended product.

[PC

Trek](https://www.pctrek.com/)

Copyright © PC Trek. All rights reserved.
